<wizard id="disclosure.journey" start="welcome.page" rem="1.5">

    <view id="welcome.page" title="Welcome">

        <jumbotron orientation="COLUMN">
            <title-large>Welcome to Hell!</title-large>
            <paragraph flavour="MUTED">Where we try to makes things as <span flavour="DANGER">painful</span> as
                possible.
            </paragraph>
        </jumbotron>

        <paragraph>
            Well, the time has come. You've died... You may have noticed. And... you're a sinner. Well, don't feel so
            bad. Who isn't these days? What with all the rules and regulations, and not even to mention the
            temptations! You will find no judgement here! Well personal judgement that is. Every sinner must be
            judged, you understand. Rules are rules. Please take a
            few minutes to complete this online questionnaire. The questionnaire aims to work out a score based on how
            bad you have been, and depending on your score, we will be able to find you your place within hell's various
            levels. There are a lot of sinners to get through, hence we have tried to automate the process somewhat.
        </paragraph>

        <div orientation="ROW" alignItems="CENTER">
            <title-large justifySelf="START">Now let's get started.</title-large>
            <link view="accessibility.page" rem="1.5" justifySelf="END">Accessibility Options</link>
        </div>

        <button-large flavour="PRIMARY">Click Here</button-large>

        <route-mappings>
            <default view="gender.page"/>
        </route-mappings>
    </view>

    <view id="accessibility.page" title="Accessibility">

        <title-large>We are here to help!</title-large>

        <paragraph>
            Disabled are you?  Well don't you worry, hell is ready for you!  Many of our residents are disabled.
            In fact many of our residents become disabled.  Anyway, if you wish to apply for your place in hell
            by phone please call the number below!
        </paragraph>

        <well>0800-HELL-IS-NOT-FOR-ME</well>

        <paragraph >
            Just a little dark humour there with the number selection.  (Apologies if you are blind.  No pun intended.)
            Had to bump off some old lady and send her on
            her way to get it.  Anyway, once you've called that number please follow the instructions below.  Listening
            to the voice instructions can take a little while.  We do our best to help.
        </paragraph>

        <well>
            <div orientation="COLUMN" em="0.8" fontStyle="ITALIC">
                <span>Wait for the beep and then push 7.</span>
                <span>Wait for the beep and then push 2.</span>
                <span>Wait for the beep and then push 3.</span>
                <span>Wait for the beep and then push 1.</span>
                <span>Wait for the beep and then push 14.</span>
                <span>Wait for the beep and then push 5.</span>
                <span>Wait for the beep and then push 8. Wait for the connection.</span>
                <span>Wait for the beep and then push 3.</span>
                <span>Wait for the beep and then push 1.</span>
                <span>Wait for the beep and then push 4.</span>
                <span>Wait for the beep and then push 2.</span>
                <span>Wait for the beep and then push 11.</span>
                <span>Wait for the beep and then push 3.</span>
                <span>Wait for the beep and then push 3.</span>
                <span>Wait for the beep and then push 4.</span>
                <span>Wait for the beep and then push 5.</span>
                <span>Wait for the beep and then push 6.</span>
                <span>Wait for the beep and then push 2.</span>
                <span>Wait for the beep and then push 1.</span>
                <span>Wait for the beep and then push 8.</span>
                <span>Wait for the beep and then push 5.</span>
                <span>Wait for the beep and then push 53.</span>
                <span>Wait for the beep and then push 3.</span>
                <span>And then push 8.  You have now entered the Welcome-To-Hell enrolment system.</span>
                <span>At this point there will be some preliminary questions to answer.  Please listen carefully to the instructions...</span>
                <span>...which will be in Belarusian.  If you wanted English, you should have picked 3 at line 8 in the list above.</span>
            </div>
        </well>

        <paragraph flavour="MUTED" fontStyle="ITALIC" fontWeight="LIGHTER" rem="1" >
            Calls will be charged at 55k pounds per minute on a land line.  If you call by mobile phone
            your cell provider may charge additional fees.  Terms and conditions apply.  No refunds or appeals accepted.
        </paragraph>

    </view>

    <view id="gender.page" title="Gender">

        <title-large>Before we get started!</title-large>

        <paragraph>
            What gender are you?  Yes, we do need to know.  Like any great club, we always have a shortage of girls.
            And there is no cover charge!  That is... if you are female.  On the other hand, you could always lie to me.
            in which case I could make it so you told me the truth after all!
        </paragraph>

        <question>What gender are you?</question>

        <options data="gender" type="STRING">
            <paragraph>Please answer truthfully and honestly.</paragraph>
            <paragraph flavour="MUTED" em="0.8">
                And please don't bother me with difficult questions about transvestites or transgenders.  This isn't
                a philosophy class you know?  This is hell!
            </paragraph>
            <div orientation="ROW">
                <option value="MALE">Male</option>
                <option value="FEMALE">Female</option>
            </div>

        </options>

        <button-large flavour="PRIMARY">Proceed</button-large>

        <route-mappings>
            <default view="like-marmite.page"/>
        </route-mappings>
    </view>

    <view id="like-marmite.page" title="Like Marmite">

        <title-large>Let's commence!</title-large>

        <paragraph>
            As you can probably understand, we want to expedite matters as much as possible. The online
            service has to service a hell of a lot of sinners! To that end, we have some preliminary questions to get
            through. And depending on your answers, we may skip some of the on-boarding process. I know you are anxious
            about your placement.
        </paragraph>

        <question>Do you like marmite?</question>

        <options data="like-marmite" type="BOOLEAN">
            <paragraph>Please answer truthfully and honestly.</paragraph>
            <paragraph flavour="MUTED" em="0.8">
                If you lie to us, we will punish you.  On the other hand, if you are honest, we will punish you anyway!  This is hell.
            </paragraph>
            <div orientation="ROW">
                <option value="true">Yes</option>
                <option value="false">No</option>
            </div>

        </options>

        <button-large flavour="PRIMARY">Proceed</button-large>

        <route-mappings>
            <rule condition="like-marmite = true" view="crazy.page"/>
            <rule condition="like-marmite = false" view="been-to-opera.page"/>
        </route-mappings>
    </view>

    <view id="crazy.page" title="Crazy">
        <title-large>Oh you poor sod.</title-large>

        <paragraph>
            Yeah.  We don't punish the mentally ill.  You can go.
        </paragraph>

        <button-large flavour="PRIMARY">Proceed</button-large>

        <route-mappings>
            <default view="escape.page"/>
        </route-mappings>
    </view>

    <view id="been-to-opera.page" title="Been to Opera">

        <title-large>Okay, next question!</title-large>

        <paragraph>
            Ok. You seem sane enough.
        </paragraph>

        <question>Have you ever been to opera?</question>

        <options data="been-to-opera" type="BOOLEAN">
            <paragraph>Answer Yes if you have ever attended an opera.</paragraph>
            <paragraph flavour="MUTED" em="0.8">
                Yes.  Simple enough question.  If you have ever attended any Operas.  Particularly any operas sung
                exclusively in italian?
            </paragraph>

            <div orientation="ROW">
                <option value="true">Yes</option>
                <option value="false">No</option>
            </div>
        </options>

        <button-large flavour="PRIMARY">Proceed</button-large>

        <route-mappings>
            <rule condition="been-to-opera = true" view="done-time.page"/>
            <rule condition="been-to-opera = false" view="like-ballet.page"/>
        </route-mappings>

    </view>

    <view id="done-time.page" title="Done Time">
        <title-large>My commiserations</title-large>

        <paragraph>
            You've already done your time.  You can go.
        </paragraph>

        <button-large flavour="PRIMARY">Proceed</button-large>

        <route-mappings>
            <default view="escape.page"/>
        </route-mappings>
    </view>

    <view id="like-ballet.page" title="Like Ballet">
        <title-large>Okay, next question!</title-large>

        <paragraph>
            Ok. Final question of our screening section.  Do you like oogling young ladies dancing around in tights
            on stage?
        </paragraph>

        <question>Do you like the ballet?</question>

        <options data="like-ballet" type="BOOLEAN">
            <paragraph>Answer Yes if you like ballet?</paragraph>
            <paragraph flavour="MUTED" em="0.8">
                Yes.  You know...  Lots of women in tights dancing and prancing around on stage?  That sort of thing.
            </paragraph>

            <div orientation="ROW">
                <option value="true">Yes</option>
                <option value="false">No</option>
            </div>
        </options>

        <button-large flavour="PRIMARY">Proceed</button-large>

        <route-mappings>
            <rule condition="like-ballet = true" view="lowest-level.page"/>
            <rule condition="like-ballet = false" view="jurisdiction.page"/>
        </route-mappings>
    </view>

    <view id="lowest-level.page" title="Good Bye">

        <title-large>You dirty dog!</title-large>

        <paragraph>
            Ahh fantastic! Straight to the bottom of hell for you. Thanks for being so kind as to skip the bureaucratic
            stuff. You've made my life much easier. Wish I could return the favour, (even considering your
            proclivities) but you know how it is. Please don't enjoy your eternal stay with us.
        </paragraph>

        <button-large flavour="PRIMARY">Proceed</button-large>

        <route-mappings>
            <default view="final.page"/>
        </route-mappings>
    </view>


    <view id="jurisdiction.page" title="Jurisdiction">
        <title-large>You dead people are so difficult!</title-large>

        <paragraph>
            You could have made life much easier for me.  Do you know how many sinners I have to get through?  That's minus
            2 points for you matey.  Because... you didn't wipe your feet when you came in...!!!   Did you now?  Exactly!
            Don't bother denying it.  I've heard it ALL before!  *sign*  Okay, lets get started.  Umm, now let me
            see, the first section is titled 'Jurisdiction'.  Ahem...  And it seems related to beliefs...otherwise known
            as facts and mor...!  What the hell is that?  I need to get my glasses checked!.   Never heard of it.
            Well never mind this legal sophistry.  This section boils down to a simple question.
        </paragraph>

        <question>What religion are you?</question>

        <options flavour="MUTED" data="religion" type="STRING">
            <option value="MUSLIM" justifySelf="START">Muslim</option>
            <option value="HINDU" justifySelf="START">Hindu</option>
            <option value="BUDDHIST" justifySelf="START">Buddhist</option>
            <option value="JEWISH" justifySelf="START">Jewish</option>
            <option value="PIRATE" justifySelf="START">Pirate</option>
            <option value="JEDI" justifySelf="START">Jedi</option>
            <option value="CHRISTIAN" justifySelf="START">Christian</option>
            <option value="ATHEIST" justifySelf="START">Atheist</option>
        </options>

        <button-large flavour="PRIMARY">Proceed</button-large>

        <route-mappings>
            <rule condition="religion = 'MUSLIM'" view="good-bye.page">
                <variable name="title">You can go!</variable>
                <variable name="narrative">
                    Sorry, we can't admit you at the moment.  The requirement for all Muslims to spend eternity in hell
                    with 70 mother-in-laws is causing some logistic difficulties.
                </variable>
            </rule>
            <rule condition="(religion = 'HINDU') or (religion = 'BUDDHIST')" view="reincarnation.page"/>
            <rule condition="religion = 'JEWISH'" view="profession-of-innocence-first.page">
                <variable name="title">Welcome to Sheol!</variable>
                <variable name="narrative">
                    Oh hello!  Old testament rules for you then.  I love the old testament...  Before they went and ruined it all!
                    Things were simpler back then.  And yes, I realise you should be in Sheol or wherever you Jewish people go when
                    you die, but face it....!  You are only one people and you've never really tried to... expand like other
                    religions.  Do you know what the maintenance bills are on a place like Hell?  So we've had to economise.
                    And well... Hell - Sheol... what's the difference?
                </variable>
            </rule>
            <rule condition="religion = 'PIRATE'" view="profession-of-innocence-first.page">
                <variable name="title">Arggh Matey!</variable>
                <variable name="narrative">
                    *sign*. If there is one thing that really gets me annoyed, its sophisticated pedants wanting to
                    make a point.  I ask you?  Is this the time?  Not only that, but I'm sure his Lordship takes exception
                    to being referred to as, in some sense, a 'meatball'.  And no!  Holidays are on Sundays, not Fridays!
                    And for Hell's Sake, remove the fake moustache.
                </variable>
            </rule>
            <rule condition="religion = 'CHRISTIAN'" view="profession-of-innocence-first.page">
                <variable name="title">Ohh bother!</variable>
                <variable name="narrative">
                    Some people insist on being difficult.  Alright then.  That's the jurisdiction question answered.
                    You will be happy (unhappy) to know that 'Yes', we can process your application.  On to the next
                    section then.  The next section is titled 'Statement of Case'.  This is where you get to enter a
                    guilt or innocence plea.  Not that there is much difference really.  Sure... sure!  You could enter
                    'innocent', but lets face it, did you ever, as the poet said, 'do the beast with two backs'?
                    Hmmm...??? Perhaps in desperate circumstances you used a sock?  Exactly, hardly innocent are you?
                </variable>
            </rule>
            <rule condition="(religion = 'JEDI') and (gender = 'MALE')" view="star-wars.page"/>
            <rule condition="(religion = 'JEDI') and (gender = 'FEMALE')" view="girl-star-wars.page"/>

            <rule condition="religion = 'ATHEIST'" view="profession-of-innocence-first.page">
                <variable name="title">LOLz</variable>
                <variable name="narrative">Ha ha!! Hee hee,  Ha ha ha.... ... ha ha hee ho ha ha...  *gasps for air*
                    Ha ha ha ha!  Oh my side!  I've a pain in my side!  Let me catch my breath.
                </variable>
            </rule>
        </route-mappings>
    </view>


    <view id="girl-star-wars.page" title="Cosplay">
        <title-large>But you're a girl!</title-large>
        <paragraph>
            What?  A girl Star Wars fan? Impossible!  Aren't you all interested in dollies and cupcakes!  You can't
            be a Star Wars fan.  Um... that is unless you are into cosplay?  I guess you could be into cosplay.
            That fits... I suppose.
        </paragraph>

        <question>Are you in to cosplay?</question>

        <options data="cosplay" type="BOOLEAN">
            <paragraph>Please answer truthfully and honestly.</paragraph>
            <paragraph flavour="MUTED" em="0.8">
                What is cosplay?  If you have to ask, then just say 'No' in the checkbox below.
            </paragraph>
            <div orientation="ROW">
                <option value="true">Yes</option>
                <option value="false">No</option>
            </div>

        </options>

        <button-large flavour="PRIMARY">Proceed</button-large>

        <route-mappings>
            <rule condition="cosplay = true" view="motoko-kusanagi.page"/>
            <rule condition="cosplay = false" view="profession-of-innocence-first.page">
                <variable name="title">I knew it!</variable>
                <variable name="narrative">
                    You just said you were a 'Jedi' in an effort to be obstructionist.  Well we are not
                    fooled.  No get-out-of-hell free card for you.  Moving onto the next section...  Here... Have a cupcake!
                </variable>
            </rule>
        </route-mappings>

    </view>

    <view id="motoko-kusanagi.page" title="Motoko Kusanagi">
        <title-large>Into cosplay?</title-large>

        <paragraph>
            Oh, so you are into cosplay?  That's cool... Just one more question.
        </paragraph>

        <question>Have you ever dressed up as Motoko Kusanagi?</question>

        <options data="motoko" type="BOOLEAN">
            <paragraph>Please answer truthfully and honestly.</paragraph>
            <paragraph flavour="MUTED" em="0.8">
                Please answer 'Yes', if you have ever dressed up as Motoko Kusanagi and exhibited yourself in front of
                hundreds, nay, thousands of horny star wars fans at a comic convention.  Otherwise, answer 'No'.
            </paragraph>
            <div orientation="ROW">
                <option value="true">Yes</option>
                <option value="false">No</option>
            </div>
        </options>

        <button-large flavour="PRIMARY">Proceed</button-large>

        <route-mappings>
            <default view="star-wars.page"/>
        </route-mappings>

    </view>

    <view id="star-wars.page" title="Star Wars">
        <title-large>These are not the droids you are looking for?</title-large>
        <paragraph>
            #if($gender == 'FEMALE')
                Okay, I admit.  That question about Motoko Kusanagi isn't really relevant. But okay,
                Okay, okay.  So you could possibly be a Star Wars fan.  Well lets see!
            #else
            If you are a true Star Wars fan you must have seen Episode 1.  In which case you have already been to
            hell... But that's only if you are a true Star Wars fan.  If you can answer these questions you may just win
            yourself a get-out-of-hell free card.
            #end

        </paragraph>

        <question>What is the name of Boba Fett's ship?</question>

        <input data="boba-fett-ship" type="STRING">
            <paragraph>Please enter in the field below the name of Boba Fett's ship?</paragraph>
        </input>

        <question>What is the name of the first ship you see in Episode 4?</question>

        <input data="first-ship" type="STRING">
            <paragraph>Please enter in the field below the name of the ship?</paragraph>
        </input>

        <button-large flavour="PRIMARY">Proceed</button-large>

        <route-mappings>
            <rule condition="(boba-fett-ship ~ '[Ss][Ll][Aa][Vv][Ee] ([Oo][Nn][Ee]|I|1)') and (first-ship ~ '[Cc][Oo][Rr][Ee][Ll][Ll][Ii][Aa][Nn] [Cc][Oo][Rr][Vv][Ee][Tt][Tt][Ee]') " view="good-bye.page">
                <variable name="title">Oh you've already done your time!</variable>
                <variable name="narrative">I know!  Episode 1 was pretty rough.  Oh well, Rogue One was better.</variable>
            </rule>
            <default view="profession-of-innocence-first.page">
                <variable name="title">You are not a Jedi!</variable>
                <variable name="narrative">
                    Oh can't answer those questions hey?  Fraud!  Imposter!  You just said you were a 'Jedi' in an effort
                    to be obstructionist.  We know everything, and No!, you are not entitled to privacy!
                </variable>
            </default>
        </route-mappings>
    </view>

    <view id="good-bye.page" title="Get Out Of Here">
        <title-large>$title</title-large>
        <paragraph>$narrative</paragraph>

        <button-large flavour="PRIMARY">Proceed</button-large>

        <route-mappings>
            <default view="escape.page"/>
        </route-mappings>
    </view>

    <view id="reincarnation.page" title="How is Hell">
        <title-large>How is that going?</title-large>
        <paragraph>
            Oh, so you're #if( $religion == 'HINDU') Hindu#else Buddhist#end?   Well in that case you are already in
            your afterlife.  How is that going for you?
        </paragraph>

        <input data="life-score" type="INTEGER">
            <paragraph>Please input a literal between 0 and -20.</paragraph>
            <paragraph flavour="MUTED" em="0.8">
                Why do I care?  Well, its for ONS reasons.  We are trying to get some stats data how the living feel
                life is going.  We've long suspected that hell isn't soo bad!  And depending on your answer, we can
                prove it using Statistics!  And remember the glass is always half empty!
            </paragraph>
        </input>

        <button-large flavour="PRIMARY">Proceed</button-large>

        <route-mappings>
            <default view="escape.page"/>
        </route-mappings>
    </view>


    <view id="profession-of-innocence-first.page" title="Innocence Declaration">
        <title-large>$title</title-large>

        <paragraph>$narrative</paragraph>

        <question>Are you innocent?</question>

        <options data="plea" type="BOOLEAN" flavour="MUTED">
            <paragraph>Please state whether you wish to enter a plea of innocence, or admit your guilt.</paragraph>
            <paragraph flavour="MUTED" em="0.8">
                Of course, if you admit your guilt, things will go... not 'well' for you, perhaps 'better' is the right
                term?  Even that is too positive.  'Better' is positively upbeat.  How about 'not as painfully as otherwise'?
            </paragraph>

            <div orientation="ROW">
                <option value="true">Yes</option>
                <option value="false">No</option>
            </div>
        </options>

        <button-large flavour="PRIMARY">Proceed</button-large>

        <route-mappings>
            <rule condition="plea = true" view="profession-of-innocence-second.page"/>
            <rule condition="plea = false" view="declare-sins.page">
                <variable name="title">Welcome #if ($gender == 'FEMALE')Sister#{else}Brother#end!</variable>
                <variable name="narrative">
                    Right first time! We are going to get along famously! None of these mealy mouthed excuses. I like a man who
                    knows what he is. You and I are going to spend eternity together, and I'm going to invite you to all the
                    best parties.  Welcome...  Mi casa es tu casa!
                </variable>
            </rule>
        </route-mappings>

    </view>

    <view id="profession-of-innocence-second.page" title="Innocence Declaration Again">
        <title-large>Are you sure?</title-large>

        <paragraph>
            Aren't we all? Aren't we all! But come now. Between the two of us, you wouldn't be here if you were
            innocent, now would you? One last try!
        </paragraph>

        <question>Are you sure you're innocent?</question>

        <options data="plea" type="BOOLEAN" flavour="MUTED">
            <paragraph>Please state whether you wish to enter a plea of innocence, or admit your guilt.</paragraph>
            <paragraph flavour="MUTED" em="0.8">
                Think man!  What proof do you have of your innocence?  Wouldn't it be better now to just admit your guilt?
            </paragraph>

            <div orientation="ROW">
                <option value="true">Yes</option>
                <option value="false">No</option>
            </div>
        </options>

        <button-large flavour="PRIMARY">Proceed</button-large>

        <route-mappings>
            <rule condition="plea = true" view="final-inocence-challenge.page">

            </rule>
            <rule condition="plea = false" view="declare-sins.page">
                <variable name="title">Welcome welcome!</variable>
                <variable name="narrative">
                    You seem a little uncertain there.  But I admire someone who is willing to admit that they are wrong
                    about being right... That is... they are right about being wrong... Err well I admire someone who is just
                    wrong.  And knows it...  Unfortunately you don't seem so certain about that.  But at least you are right
                    now.  Or right this time.
                </variable>
            </rule>
        </route-mappings>
    </view>

    <view id="final-inocence-challenge.page" title="Final Innocence Challenge">
        <title-large>Oh come on...!!??</title-large>

        <paragraph>
            You can't tell me you have never sinned ever in your life? Not even once?  What about that time you
            pinched Sally in the playground when you were four?
        </paragraph>

        <question>Did you pinch Sally when you were four?</question>

        <options data="pinched-sally" type="BOOLEAN" flavour="MUTED">
            <paragraph>Please state whether pinched Sally in the playground when you were four.</paragraph>
            <paragraph flavour="MUTED" em="0.8">
                And please don't lie!
            </paragraph>

            <div orientation="COLUMN">
                <option value="true">Yes! Ok I did it.</option>
                <option value="false">Never in life!  My name is Mohammed Zerhouni! I didn't know any Sallys at that age.</option>
            </div>
        </options>

        <button-large flavour="PRIMARY">Proceed</button-large>

        <route-mappings>
            <rule condition="pinched-sally = true" view="declare-sins.page">
                <variable name="title">I knew it!</variable>
                <variable name="narrative">
                    You should be ashamed of yourself, trying to get out of hell after that one.
                </variable>
                <variable name="plea">true</variable>
            </rule>
            <rule condition="pinched-sally = false" view="date-of-death.page">
                <variable name="title">Still hey?</variable>
                <variable name="narrative">
                    Didn't pinch Sally hey?  Well I don't believe you.  Everybody knows a Sally, especially at age four.
                    Oh well.  Let's move on.  What is your date of death?
                </variable>
            </rule>
        </route-mappings>

    </view>


    <view id="declare-sins.page" title="Sins Declaration">
        <title-large>$title</title-large>

        <paragraph>$narrative</paragraph>

        <question>Please declare your sins</question>

        <input data="sin-1" type="STRING">
            <paragraph>Please declare your first sin.</paragraph>
        </input>

        <input data="sin-2" type="STRING">
            <paragraph>Please declare your second sin. (If you don't have any further sins, then leave blank)</paragraph>
        </input>

        <input data="sin-3" type="STRING">
            <paragraph>Please declare your third sin. (If you don't have any further sins, then leave blank)</paragraph>
        </input>

        <input data="sin-4" type="STRING">
            <paragraph>Please declare your forth sin. (If you don't have any further sins, then leave blank)</paragraph>
        </input>

        <paragraph>
            If you have any further sins, then don't bother putting them in.  Four is quite enough.
        </paragraph>

        <button-large flavour="PRIMARY">Proceed</button-large>

        <route-mappings>
            <default view="date-of-death.page">
                <variable name="title">Great Cahoonies!</variable>
                <variable name="narrative">
                    Wow.  You've been bad.  Welcome! Hehe.  You gonna P-A-Y for those ones bruv.  Especially the...
                    first one!  And look! You've left a few out.
                </variable>
            </default>
        </route-mappings>

    </view>

    <view id="date-of-death.page" title="Date of Death">
        <title-large>$title</title-large>

        <paragraph>$narrative</paragraph>

        <question>What is your date of death?</question>

        <input data="date-of-death" type="DATE">
            <paragraph>Please state the date of your death.</paragraph>
            <paragraph flavour="MUTED" em="0.8">
                This is primarily to determine which set of rules to judge you by. Yes... the rules do change. Unlike some
                religions, we do recognize that morality is grey and is affected by the circumstances of the times.
                For example, being sexist in the 80s is hardly a crime, but now-a-days we can get you for that too. Progress...
            </paragraph>

        </input>

        <button-large flavour="PRIMARY">Proceed</button-large>

        <route-mappings>
            <default view="payment.page"/>
        </route-mappings>
    </view>


    <view id="payment.page" title="Time to Pay">
        <title-large>Time to Pay</title-large>

        <paragraph>Yes!  Time to dig deep my friends.  Hell costs money.  Time to look out all those spondoolies,
            buckazoids, greens and mulas you have.  Be sure to look under your eyelids.  A lot of dead people have some
            bucks stashed there.  And under your tongue.
        </paragraph>

        <question>What currency do you wish use to make payment?</question>

        <options data="payment" type="STRING" flavour="MUTED">
            <paragraph>Please enter your method of payment.</paragraph>
            <paragraph flavour="MUTED" em="0.8">
                Payment is 2 coins of various currencies.  Be sure to select the currency you have available below.
            </paragraph>

            <div orientation="COLUMN">
                <option value="HEAVENLY-HALF-PENNIES">2 Heavenly Halfpennies</option>
                <option value="DEVILISH-DOLLARS">2 Devilish Dollars</option>
                <option value="EARTHLY-FIAT">2 Of whatever they are using for fiat on earth these days</option>
                <option value="GOLD">2 Gold Coins</option>
                <option value="NOTHING">Nothing - I got no money! - Does that mean I can go home and skip all this HELL malarkey?</option>
            </div>
        </options>

        <button-large flavour="PRIMARY">Proceed</button-large>

        <route-mappings>
            <rule condition="payment = 'HEAVENLY-HALF-PENNIES'" view="apply-for-appeal.page">
                <variable name="title">Not Acceptable</variable>
                <variable name="narrative">
                    Sorry (well not really), but we don't accept any of the Heavenly currencies here.  No market for exchange you see.
                </variable>
            </rule>
            <rule condition="payment = 'EARTHLY-FIAT'" view="apply-for-appeal.page">
                <variable name="title">No Acceptable</variable>
                <variable name="narrative">
                    Haha.  You know how much that stuff is worth?
                </variable>
            </rule>
            <rule condition="payment = 'DEVILISH-DOLLARS'" view="devilish-payment.page">

            </rule>
            <rule condition="payment = 'GOLD'" view="apply-for-appeal.page">
                <variable name="title">No Acceptable</variable>
                <variable name="narrative">
                    Wish I could, but you only paid 2 gold coins.  It just ain't worth much these days.
                </variable>
            </rule>
            <rule condition="payment = 'NOTHING'" view="apply-for-appeal.page">
                <variable name="title">That's too bad</variable>
                <variable name="narrative">
                    And no, you don't get to go home. You get a nice rack all made out for you in one of our pits.
                </variable>
            </rule>
        </route-mappings>
    </view>

    <view id="devilish-payment.page" title="VIP Section" >
        <title-large>Welcome!  To our VIP section.</title-large>

        <paragraph>
            Welcome Sir.  Welcome to an eternity of carnal delights.  As one of our VIP members you will receive the
            benefit of your own hellish dwelling, where servants will service your every need.  Consider this the first rung
            of your climb up the greasy pole. Err... mixing my metaphors there.  Hell there might even be an ex boy friend or
            girl friend who may beg to be your servant for eternity. Welcome to the club!
        </paragraph>

        <button-large flavour="PRIMARY">Proceed</button-large>

        <route-mappings>
            <default view="final.page">
            </default>
        </route-mappings>
    </view>

    <view id="apply-for-appeal.page" title="Appeal" >
        <title-large>$title</title-large>

        <paragraph>$narrative</paragraph>

        <question>Do you wish to appeal?</question>

        <options data="apply-for-appeal" type="BOOLEAN">
            <paragraph>This is your change to apply for someone to intercede on your behalf.  </paragraph>
            <paragraph flavour="MUTED" em="0.8">
                Yes.  We do allow appeals, even though you haven't really been sentenced yet.  Well okay you are going
                to hell, but which level is not really determined yet.  And the appeal process is completely anonymous.
                We will not remember or take into account whatever option you choose. We are impartial.
            </paragraph>

            <div orientation="ROW">
                <option value="false">No</option>
                <option value="false">No</option>
            </div>
        </options>

        <button-large flavour="PRIMARY">Proceed</button-large>

        <route-mappings>
            <default view="thrall-of-hell.page">
                <variable name="title">Apply to be a thrall of hell today!</variable>
                <variable name="narrative">
                   *Sign*  Now that horrible business about appeals is done. We have a limited offer.  You are going to
                    hell and you are going deep my friend... Deep into hell, based on the dirt we have on you.
                </variable>
            </default>
        </route-mappings>
    </view>

    <view id="thrall-of-hell.page" title="Thrall of Hell">
        <title-large>$title</title-large>

        <paragraph>$narrative</paragraph>

        <question>Do you wish to apply to be a thrall of a lord-of-Hell?</question>

        <options data="apply-thrall" type="BOOLEAN">
            <paragraph>Answer Yes, if you wish to submit your application to the various lords of hell. No otherwise.</paragraph>
            <paragraph flavour="MUTED" em="0.8">
                Being a thrall can be a rewarding or costly experience. It all depends really, on who takes you as their thrall.
                There is even a chance that you have a previous girl-friend or boy-friend that is possibly evil enough
                that they are a lord-of-hell by now. That could be both good and bad.
            </paragraph>

            <div orientation="ROW">
                <option value="true">Yes</option>
                <option value="false">No</option>
            </div>
        </options>

        <button-large flavour="PRIMARY">Proceed</button-large>
        <route-mappings>
            <rule condition="apply-thrall = true" view="thrall-results.page"/>
            <rule condition="apply-thrall = false" view="booking.page">
                <variable name="title">Not going to try?</variable>
                <variable name="narrative">
                    Yeah I wouldn't bother either.  They are a prickly lot.  And who knows, being a thrall may not be
                    such a good deal anyway.
                </variable>
            </rule>
        </route-mappings>
    </view>

    <view id="thrall-results.page" title="Thrall Results">
        <title-large>Thrall Results</title-large>

        <paragraph>Ok.  We've submitted your application to be a thrall.  The results have come in.  Here they are.</paragraph>

        <table>
            <row>
                <column>Lord</column><column>Accepted</column><column>Reason</column>
            </row>
            <row>
                <cell>Mephisto</cell><cell>Negative</cell><cell>Too weak.</cell>
            </row>
            <row>
                <cell>Diablo</cell><cell>Denied</cell><cell>Not smart enough.</cell>
            </row>
            <row>
                <cell>Baal</cell><cell>Negatory</cell><cell>Too fat.</cell>
            </row>
            <row>
                <cell>T. Blair</cell><cell>Nope</cell><cell>Not sexy enough.</cell>
            </row>
            <row>
                <cell>A. Greenspan</cell><cell>Never</cell><cell>No positions available at this time.</cell>
            </row>
        </table>

        <button-large flavour="PRIMARY">Proceed</button-large>

        <route-mappings>
            <default view="booking.page">
                <variable name="title">Oh... My commiserations</variable>
                <variable name="narrative">
                    Yeah, I know.  It always sucks being the last one selected for the team.  Too bad.  Really... I
                    though Greenspan had a few positions available.  Anywho... Onto booking your place.  There are many levels to
                    hell and the higher levels can fill out pretty quick.
                </variable>
            </default>
        </route-mappings>
    </view>


    <view id="booking.page" title="Booking">
        <title-large>$title</title-large>

        <paragraph>$narrative</paragraph>

        <paragraph>
            The results of our deliberations regarding your placement in hell, based in part, rather wholly, on your
            declaration of innocence and your various sins and definitely not on any of your attemps to weasel out of
            hell, and the various times you have lied. Lied in fact, to me...  Anyway, based wholly as an impartial judge
            we have determined that your sins warrant a placing no higher than the 3rd level of hell.  (1 being the absolute
            lowest level.)
        </paragraph>

        <paragraph>
            We will now attempt to place you in the 3rd level of hell.  Almost full... But hey we do have a place
            available, in fact a last few... Oh look!  Your Mother in Law is down here too.  You know I'm not without heart...
            Do you wish me to find you a place next to her?
        </paragraph>

        <question>Do you wish to spend eternity next to your Mother In Law?</question>

        <options data="mother-in-law" type="BOOLEAN">
            <paragraph>Please answer Yes if you wish to spend an eternity in hell, next to your Mother In Law.  No otherwise.</paragraph>
            <paragraph flavour="MUTED" em="0.8">
                Please answer promptly, the placings are going rather quickly.
            </paragraph>

            <div orientation="ROW">
                <option value="true">Yes</option>
                <option value="false">No</option>
            </div>
        </options>

        <button-large flavour="PRIMARY">Proceed</button-large>

        <route-mappings>
            <rule condition="mother-in-law = true" view="missed-booking.page"/>
            <rule condition="mother-in-law = false" view="missed-booking.page"/>
        </route-mappings>

    </view>

    <view id="missed-booking.page" title="Missed Booking">
        <title-large>
            #if( $mother-in-law )
                What! Really?  Oh of course.
            #else
                Yeah..!
            #end

        </title-large>
        <paragraph>
            #if( $mother-in-law )
            Well of course, Family is Family right.  Excuse my surprise.  Okay lets see...
            #else
            Not surprised.  It was just a thought really.
            #end
        </paragraph>
        <paragraph>
            Oh... Awfully sorry.  That place has just gone.  Let me find another... Oh that's gone too. Err..
            Sorry pal..  But it looks like the 3rd level of hell is full at the moment.  We'll have to book you in
            at level 2.  Searching.... Oh yeah.. Much better placings here.  We'll book you right in next to a Mr N. Farage.
            Hey, no real bad characters here yet.  Just mass murderers and psychos, and other sorts with strange ideas.
        </paragraph>

        <paragraph>Ok.  That's you all booked in.  Please proceed.</paragraph>

        <button-large flavour="PRIMARY">Proceed</button-large>

        <route-mappings>
            <default view="final.page">
            </default>
        </route-mappings>
    </view>

    <view id="final.page" externalName="final"/>
    <view id="escape.page" externalName="escape"/>

</wizard>